<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Zipangu.degreeDatas.0.label>Stubborn craftsman</Zipangu.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Zipangu.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME does not care about the surroundings and is dedicating life to making things. NAME became unsociable to associate humans too much with fervor.</Zipangu.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <Zipangu.degreeDatas.1.label>Karakuri master</Zipangu.degreeDatas.1.label>
  <Zipangu.degreeDatas.1.description>NAME loves to make karakuri(old Japanese machine). HE often look for a new type of machine. And HE is passionate to dismantle machine and study.On the other hand, because butchering of animals is not interesting, it becomes appropriate.</Zipangu.degreeDatas.1.description>
  <Zipangu.degreeDatas.2.label>Kitoshi</Zipangu.degreeDatas.2.label>
  <Zipangu.degreeDatas.2.description>Kito means pray,shi means person. NAME prays everyday aiming for harmony between people and nature.Because HE does not care fine things, so HE may be able to do artistic cuisine.</Zipangu.degreeDatas.2.description>
  <Zipangu.degreeDatas.3.label>Hikyaku</Zipangu.degreeDatas.3.label>
  <Zipangu.degreeDatas.3.description>A Japanese  porter. NAME has a transportation business carrying luggage anywhere as ordered as a business. Because HE is running everyday, HE is not good at sewing and smithing which can not move the body exactly.</Zipangu.degreeDatas.3.description>

  <ZiPangu.degreeDatas.0.label>Hyakusyo</ZiPangu.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <ZiPangu.degreeDatas.0.description>A Japanese farmer. NAME lives in agriculture as a living. Because HE coexists with nature, HE is resistant to some degree of threat. However, HE cannot handle weapons well, since HE does not use weapons often.</ZiPangu.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <ZiPangu.degreeDatas.1.label>Matagi</ZiPangu.degreeDatas.1.label>
  <ZiPangu.degreeDatas.1.description>A Japanese hunter. NAME is hunting big beasts such as bears as a living. I do a lot of hard work to carry prey and dismantle. 栽培の時は力加減がわからずダメにしてしまうことがある。</ZiPangu.degreeDatas.1.description>
  <ZiPangu.degreeDatas.2.label>Bushido</ZiPangu.degreeDatas.2.label>
  <ZiPangu.degreeDatas.2.description>A Japanese soldier. From the early age NAME has been training the two ways of fighting and studing to survive the world of war. However, HE was not very good at general work as menial took care of HIM.</ZiPangu.degreeDatas.2.description>


</LanguageData>